IFEOLUWA DELE-OYERO

deleoyeroifeoluwa@gmail.com

Lekki Lagos | https://www.linkedin.com/in/ifeoluwa-dele-oyero-63411a223/ | 08146917848 | 08051613307

PROFILE

Solution-focused Frontend Developer with experience in web-based applications and Software Solutions. Participated in development and implementation of Apps, Logical and results- driven Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused Solutions for customers with various business objectives.

WORK HISTORY

Zealight Innovation Labs.

Lagos, Nigeria

FRONT-END ENGINEER

April 2022 - Present

- Developing Scalable UIs using Reactis Framework
- Consume Endpoints (APIs) and integrate on the USer-End
- Fixing of Bugs
- Deploy Codes on Git hub and some other Git Operations

T40 Technologies (Remote) 6 Months Intern.

FRONT-END ENGINEER

April 2022 - sept 2022

- Developing Scalable Ui's using Reactjs and React-strap framework.
- Consume Endpoints (APIs) and integrate on the User-End
- Deploy Logic and Fix user-end related Bugs
- Deploy codes on Bitbuckets and perform series of Git operations

SKILLUP AFRICA.

Lagos, Nigeria

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

August 2021 - Present

- <u>Using HTML, JavaScript and CSS to bring concepts to life.</u>
- Developing and maintaining the user interface.

- Implementing design on mobile websites.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability

EDUCATION

HND, Computer-Science

2020

The Polytechnic Ibadan

CERTIFICATION/TRAINING

Jobberman Soft Skills Training Certification

2022

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Computing: HTML,CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, Boostrap,ChakraUi,Sass,
- **Professional:** Problem solving, Good Communication, Great Team Spirit, Critical Thinking, Solution and Goal Oriented.
- Languages: English (Fluent), Yoruba (Fluent)

REFEREES

Available on request